http://www.thefragranceshop.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
Shop By Designer
Choose Original DesignerSee All Original DesignersThe Fragrance ShopAbercrombie & Fitch typeAcqua Di Parma typeAdidas typeAdrienne Vittadini typeAgent Provocateur typeAlfred Sung typeAnne Klein typeAnnick Goutal typeAntonia Bellanca typeAntonio Puig typeAnucci typeAramis typeAzzaro typeBalenciaga typeBalmain typeBanana Republic typeBarney's New York typeBenefit typeBenetton typeBetsey Johnson typeBeyonce typeBijan typeBill Blass typeBob Mackie typeBoadicea the Victorious typeB9 typeBorghese typeBottega Veneta typeBoucheron typeBritney Spears typeBurberry typeBulgari / Bvlgari typeByblos typeByredo typeBy Kilian typeCabochard typeCacharel typeCalvin Klein typeCananli typeCarolina Herrera typeCaron typeCartier typeCarven typeCatherine Deneuve typeCeline Dion typeCharles of the Ritz typeCher typeChloe typeChopard typeChristian Audigier typeChristian Louboutin typeClarins typeClean typeClinique typeClive Christian typeCoach typeComme Des Garcons typeCoty typeCourreges typeCreed typeChristian Louboutin typeCzech & Speake typeDana typeDavid Beckham typeDavidoff typeDiane Von Furstenberg typeDiesel typeDiptyque typeDolce & Gabbana typeDonna Karan typeDunhill typeEddie Bauer typeElizabeth Arden typeElizabeth Taylor typeEllen Tracy typeEmanuel Ungaro typeEmporio Armani typeErox typeEscada typeEscentric Molecules typeEstee Lauder typeFamous French Designer typeFragrance Du Bois typeFrances Denney typeFrances Kurkdjian typeFendi type/option>Fred Hayman typeFrench Connection typeFresh typeGabriela Sabatini typeGeoffrey Beene typeGermain Monteil typeGiorgio Armani typeGiorgio Beverly Hills typeGivenchy typeGloria Vanderbilt typeGres typeGucci typeGuerlain typeGuess typeGuy LaRoche typeGwen Stefani typeHalle Berry typeHalston typeHanae Mori typeHenri Bendel typeHelmut Lang typeHermes typeHollister typeHoubigant typeHugo Boss typeIsabella Rosselini typeIssey Miyake typeJacomo typeJaguar typeJason Wu typeJay Z typeJean Charles Brosseau typeJean Desprez typeJean D`Albret typeJean Louis Scherrer typeJean Patou typeJean Paul Gaultier typeJennifer Aniston typeJennifer Lopez typeJessica McClintock typeJessica Simpson typeJimmy Choo typeJo Malone typeJohn Varvatos typeJoop typeJuicy Couture typeKarl Lagerfeld typeKat Von D typeKate Spade typeKeihl's typeKenneth Cole typeKenzo typeKim Kardashian typeKimora Lee Simmons typeKrizia typeLa Perla typeLacoste typeLalique typeLancaster typeLancome typeLanvin typeLaura Ashley typeLaura Biagiotti typeLe Labo typeLiz Claiborne typeLolita Lempicka typeLouis Vuitton typeLucky Brand typeLyon typeMarc Jacobs typeMarcella Borghese typeMarilyn Miglin typeMary J Blige typeMaurer & Wirtz typeMichael Kors typeMichel Germain typeMillot typeMolinard typeMont Blanc typeMoschino typeMuelhens typeNarciso Rodriguez typeNautica typeNicole Miller typeNina Ricci typeNino Cerruti typeOcean Pacific typeOscar de la Renta typePaco Rabanne typePaloma Picasso type
Parumes de Marly typeParis Hilton typePatti Labelle typePaul Sebastian typePaul Smith typePenhaligon typePerry Ellis typePharrell typePhilosophy typePino Silvestre typePrada typePrescriptives typePriscilla Presley typePrivilege typeQueen Latifah typeRalph Lauren typeRemy Latour typeRevlon typeRobert Piguet typeRoberto Cavalli typeRochas typeRoja Dove typeRomeo Gigli typeRoyal Copenhagen typeSarah Jessica Parker typeScott McClintock typeSean John typeSentiment typeSerge Luten typeShiseido typeShulton typeSonia Rykiel typeStella McCartney typeSwiss Army typeTed Lapidus typeThe Fragrance ShopThierry Mugler typeTiffany typeTokyo Milk typeTom Ford typeTommy Bahama typeTommy Hilfiger typeTory Burch type Tova typeTrue Religion typeUsher typeValentino typeVan Cleef & Arpels typeVera Wang typeVersace typeVictoria`s Secret typeViktor & Rolf typeVince Comuto typeVisconti di Modrone typeWeil typeWorth typeXerjoff typeYves Saint Laurent type
Shop By Category
Samplers & Bundles
Designer Fragrances
Women's Designers
Men's Designers
Unisex Designers
Rare & Discontinued
Exclusive Designer Fragrances
Fragrance Finder
What's Wrong With Your Fragrance?
Hassle-Free Returns
How To Use Our Oils
All About Us In 30 Seconds
Customer Comments
Watch Our Videos
TFS Gift Cards
Wish Lists
Get Social
Write A Review
Share Us With Friends
Follow Us on Twitter
Sign Up via Email
Like Us on Facebook
Privacy Policy
The Fragrance Shop respects your privacy and the security of your personal information. For this reason, we have updated our Privacy Policy (“Policy”) as of July 7, 2018. It describes the information we collect, how we use it and what choices you have. This Policy applies when you access our websites and mobile applications, shop in our Retail Stores and Outlets, contact us by phone, email, and chat or connect with us in any other manner, including in our social media channels.
You are always welcome to contact us about your privacy, whether you have questions or to provide feedback.
Contact us:
by phone: U.S. and Canada: (888) 377-3677
by phone from outside the U.S.: Access Code + (704) 895-5903
by email:  us@thefragranceshop.com
by mail: The Fragrance Shop, 200 North Greensboro St, A10 Carrboro NC 27510
To make sure we continue to offer the best service possible, your communication with The Fragrance Shop may be monitored for quality assurance.
Information We Collect
Information you share with us: We collect and store the information you provide to us. For example, you may provide information to us when you place an order or create an account on our websites, shop at our stores and outlets, apply for a job, enter a sweepstakes or contest, join our mailing list, take a survey, or connect with one of our customer service representatives. Types of information   you may provide to us include, for example: your name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, payment information, date of birth or pictures. If you choose to share information on our social media sites, including the posting of any pictures, please read our Content Submission Terms and Conditions. You may also share information about a gift recipient if you purchase a gift card or send a package to someone other than yourself.
Additional information we may receive: We also collect and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us via the internet. Types of information we may gather through this automatic process include your device location, IP address, browsing history and purchase history. Please see the Cookies and Pixel Tags section for additional information.
Information we gather from other sources: To best serve you, we may combine the information   you provide to us and the information gathered automatically with data is publicly available and data   we receive from other reputable sources. This includes such things as change of address information and demographic information. We work with these third parties to help us add to, verify, or correct the information   we store.
For E.U. Residents Only: Please note  if you are a resident of the European Union, we will only collect additional information via cookies and other online tools if you agree to its collection, and the sharing of such information is subject to your specific consent.
Updating Your Information
If any of your information has changed and you would like to update your customer information (name, address, telephone number, and email address), please contact us. To protect your privacy, we will need to validate your identity before we update or review your information.
Why We Collect Your Information
We collect this information for many reasons. For example, the information that you provide to The Fragrance Shop enables us to: process your order, contact you about the status of your order, send you tracking information for your packages, reserve store inventory for you, post your product review, save your purchase history, provide you with information about the products you’ve purchased, manage your online account (such as saving your wish list), mail catalogs to you, send you promotional emails, and provide you with the best possible customer service.
The additional information   we receive from you and gather from other sources allows us to serve you better and improve the overall shopping experience for all of our customers. For example, this type of information enables us to: improve the design of our website, understand shopping preferences, serve advertisements   we think may be of interest to customers, and improve upon the content of our promotional emails, our merchandise selection, and our customer service.
Sharing Your Information
We partner with third-party companies that provide certain services for us and we share your information with these companies, so   they can perform those services on our behalf. We have partners who help us with things such as shipping, name and address verification, email distribution, market research, survey distribution, The Fragrance Shop advertising across third-party platforms, promotions management, fraud protection & investigation, and payment processing (to view PayPal’s privacy policy, please visit https://www.paypal.com/privacy).
We partner with third parties, such as Facebook and Google, to serve you ads   we think may interest you. These third parties may combine the information we share with them with information already in their possession; they may also offer you choices about which ads you see on their platforms.
We also partner with third-party vendors that use analytics data for a variety of purposes such as to improve the design and content of our websites, to help us learn which pages are most attractive to all of our visitors and what promotions visitors like to see, and to gauge the success of our advertising campaigns. One such vendor is Google Analytics. Please click here for more information about how data is collected and processed in connection with the Google Analytics service: www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.
We work closely with our partners to ensure   your privacy is respected and protected and require these third parties keep your personal information secure and confidential. We may allow some of our third-party partners to use the information we share with them for their own purposes, but only if it is anonymized and aggregated, so   it cannot be linked back to any individual.
On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, when we have a good faith belief  we are required to do so by law, or where otherwise permitted by law.
We may also share your personal information in connection with or during the negotiation of any merger, financing, acquisition or dissolution transaction or proceeding involving sale, transfer, divestiture, or disclosure of all or a portion of our company or assets. If another company acquires our company or assets, that company may possess the personal information collected by us and will assume the consents and responsibilities regarding your personal information as described in this Policy.
Cookies and Pixel Tags
We gather information about how visitors navigate through our website by using clickstream data gathered with “cookies” and other online tools such as “pixel tags.”
A cookie is a small data file stored by your web browser on your computer. Session cookies are erased when the user closes the web browser or browser tab. Persistent cookies remain on your hard drive until they expire or are deleted.  Some cookies are necessary for our website’s functionality and enable you to place an item in your online shopping bag and to place an order on our website. Other cookies allow us to enhance and personalize your online shopping experience, so the information you receive is more relevant to you. Here are some examples of what cookies allows us to do: remember what items are in your shopping bag, recognize you when you return to our website, enable faster checkout if you have created an account at thefragranceshop.com, analyze how our customers navigate our website and which products they search for, and deliver personalized marketing from the Fragrance Shop. If you set your browser to refuse all cookies, please contact us directly to place your order.
We use pixel tags – tiny graphic images – to tell us what parts of our website you have visited or to measure the effectiveness of any searches you may do on our website. Pixel tags also enable us to send you email in a format you can read and let us know when you have opened an email message from us.
Some of our third-party vendors may also use cookies or other online tools such as pixel tags on our website.
We also contract with third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf across the internet. To do this, they will collect information about your visits to our website and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements. These targeted advertisements may appear on other sites that you visit. This information is collected using a cookie or pixel tag – industry standard technology used by most websites.
For E.U. Residents Only: Please note that if you are a European Union resident, we only use non-essential cookies and pixel tags (those we use for enhancement and personalization) when you opt-in to allowing for their use. However, there are some cookies that must remain in order for our website to function property (essential cookies) and these will remain in use even if you do not opt-in to our use of non-essential cookies.
Your Choices
We want you to be satisfied with our use of your information and the communications you receive from us. We are happy to honor your preference requests.
If you feel you hear from us too often or you prefer not to hear from us at all, whether by mail or by email, we are happy to change your preferences. Please contact us directly by phone, chat, email or mail.  You can also unsubscribe from our email updates using the link provided in each email. Please keep in mind if you choose not to receive these promotional emails, you will continue to receive emails from us about recent transactions, including orders and returns. You can also contact us directly, so we may make the changes on your behalf. So we can be sure to identify you correctly, please provide us with your exact name and address or the mailing label from your catalog. Because mailings and promotional emails are planned in advance, it may take several weeks for your request to become effective.
To opt-out of direct personalized advertising on the Internet from The Fragrance Shop, click here. If you choose to opt-out of direct personalized advertising, you may still see advertisements on the internet from The Fragrance Shop, however, such advertisements were not generated by use of your personal information.
For Canadian Residents Only: If you are resident of Canada and you would like to take advantage of any of your rights under the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) please contact The Fragrance Shop’s customer service department and we will be happy to assist you.
For E.U. Residents Only: If you are a resident of the European Union and you would like to take advantage of any of your rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), such as your Right to Erasure (otherwise known as the “Right to be Forgotten”) please contact The Fragrance Shop’s customer service department and we will be happy to assist you. For additional information related to EU residents, please see the European Union Residents section of this policy.
Privacy of Children
Protecting the rights of children is very important to The Fragrance Shop. Our website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use thefragranceshop.com with the help of a parent or guardian.
Links to Other Websites
Occasionally we provide links to other websites to enhance functionality and the shopping experience. These sites operate independently of The Fragrance Shop and have established their own privacy and security policies. If you choose to navigate to another website through our websites, we strongly encourage you to review the policies of those websites also.
Information Security
The Fragrance Shop maintains your information securely. It is our intent to protect against the loss, misuse, alteration, or unauthorized access of information we have collected from you or received from a partner. In order to protect it securely, we use a variety of current technologies and processes and are always working to stay current with trends in Information Security. It is our practice to use encryption or hashing whenever we receive or transmit your sensitive information
We also encourage you to educate yourself on safe internet practices. For example, to practice safe internet use, we suggest you use a strong password for your The Fragrance Shop account and change it frequently; we also suggest you sign out of your account when you are finished using it on a public or shared computer. Please note that The Fragrance Shop will never ask you for your credit card information over email.
Policy Changes
If our practices change, we will make the necessary changes to this privacy policy. We will notify you of a change to the policy by updating the date above. We encourage you to review our privacy policy periodically.
For EU Residents Only Please note that if our practices change, we will notify you of the change and, if necessary, obtain new consent.  We will only collect your information from non-essential cookies if you consent to that use.
We will only use the information you provide to us, such as the information you provide when placing an order, for our own marketing purposes if you consent to that use.  If you wish to take advantage of any of your rights pursuant to the European Union Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), such as the Right to Erasure (otherwise known as the “Right to be Forgotten”), please contact us directly and we will be happy to assist you.
If you feel our customer service department has not appropriately responded to your request pursuant to the GDPR, you may contact The Fragrance Shop’s Data Protection Officer (DPO) directly. Please send all correspondence to: Jennifer Mann, The Fragrance Shop, 200 North Greensboro St, A10 Carrboro,NC 27510 USA or by email to jennifer@thefragranceshop.com
Contact us
For questions or comments related to your privacy, we invite you to contact our customer service department. We’re always here to help.
Sign Up For TFS Emails & Offers
Sign up for special offers, new arrivals, and occasional free samples
Shop
Bundles & Samplers
Designer Fragrances
Special Blends
Single-Note Fragrances
Musks & Imported Oils
Essential Oils
Bath & Body Collection
Fragrance Families
Features
Fragrance Finder
Customer Comments
Best-Selling Fragrances
Newest Fragrances
What's Wrong with Your Perfume?
How To Use Our Oils
All About Us In 30 Seconds
Fragrance Replication
Watch Our Videos
TFS Gift Cards
Wish Lists
Service
Contact Us
Sign in or Create an account
Hassle-Free Returns
Shipping & Tracking
Can't Find What You Want?
Write A Fragrance Review
Write A Store Review
Privacy Policy
Terms and Conditions
Sitemap
Follow Us
Share Us
The designer type fragrances available here are not the Designer originals, they are our own replications in concentrated form, completely free of alcohol and other harmful fillers.
Our designer types accurately replicate the scent, but are not the original product.
All of our fragrances are created in-house, or expressly for us by a select group of boutique perfumers.
© 1996- The Fragrance Shop. All rights reserved.
